http://www.afterloss.com/privacy.html

AfterLoss Inc.
Order Form
Privacy PolicyWe are committed to safeguarding your privacy online and protecting the information that we collect. As part of the normal operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement or the practices of this site, please contact us.AfterLoss Inc.Email:   service@afterloss.comPhone: 1-800-423-8811Information We CollectCustomer Information. In order to purchase a product or service, you may be required to give us contact information (e.g. name, email address), unique identifiers (e.g. password), and demographic information (e.g. postal code). Certain information is collected in order to, among other things, verify your identity for subsequent use of our service. If you decide to purchase a product or service, we will need to collect certain financial information, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address. Financial information is used to bill you for products and services. As a visitor to our web site, you may be asked for your name and email address for various promotions. Your contact information is used to contact you when necessary, and to send you important new information about our products and services. Your account information is password-protected so that only you have external access to your personal information. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. We do not share your financial information with outside parties, other than our bank and credit card transaction service.• IP ADDRESS. We collect your Internet Protocol (IP) address each time you visit our web site. The IP address is a unique identifier assigned to your computer each time you connect to the internet. The IP address is used for site traffic statistical reporting and analysis, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to help protect our customers and ourselves from fraud.• COOKIES. Our web site uses cookies to keep temporarily stored information during a multi-page process, such as when placing an order. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from our server and stored on your computer's hard drive. You have the choice to accept all cookies, or be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies, by setting the appropriate options in your browser. We only use cookies when there is persistent data that is required to be kept from one page to another, such as when completing an order. If you decide not to accept a cookie, you may not be able to proceed with an order.• SERVER ACTIVITY. Customer logins, and other server access activities, are monitored and analyzed to protect our server from unauthorized login attempts.• CORRESPONDENCE. We reserve the right to keep a record of any correspondence (i.e. email or paper mail) submitted by you to us.Disclosure of InformationWe cannot ensure that all of your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not described in this privacy policy. For example, we may be required to disclose personally identifiable information to the government, law enforcement or legal counsel (e.g. by court order).Security MeasuresIn order to maximize protection of your information, we use state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your personal data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the internet. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.GeneralThis privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of your customer agreement.We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked web sites or other web sites hosted on our server.
©2020 Afterloss Inc.  |  Delivery  |  Privacy
About AfterLoss
Our History
Benefits for the Bereaved
Benefits for the Funeral Professional
Media
Contact Us
AfterLoss HelpLetters®
